midwayautosupply.com 2013-05-02

# Privacy Policy

Personal Information

  * When you register in Midway Auto Supply, we will ask you to provide personal information. 
  * We use cookies and other technologies to keep track of your interactions with our sites and services to offer a personalized experience. 

Uses of Information

  * We use the information we collect to provide the services you request. Our services may include the display of personalized content and advertising. 
  * We use your information to inform you of other products or services offered by Shop At Midawy.com and its affiliates, and to send you relevant survey invitations related to our services. 
  * We do not sell, rent, or lease our customer lists to third parties. In order to help provide our services, we occasionally provide information to other companies who work on our behalf. 

Write us at:

Midway Auto Supply Privacy  
P.O. Box 4415  
Dallas, TX 75208

Midway Auto Supply Privacy Statement  

Midway Auto Supply is committed to protecting your privacy. Please read the Midway Auto Supply Privacy Statement below and also any supplementary information at the end of this statement for additional details about particular Midway Auto Supply sites and services that you may use. 

This Midway Auto Supply Privacy Statement applies to data collected by Midway Auto Supply through its Midway Auto Supply sites and services; it does apply to data collected through other online or offline Midway Auto Supply sites, products or services. 

Collection of your Personal Information

In order to sign in to Shop At Midway services, you will be asked to enter an e-mail address and password, which we refer to as your Midway Auto Supply credentials. As part of creating your Midway Auto Supply credentials, you may also be requested to provide an alternate e-mail address, and questions and secret answers, which we use to verify your identity and assist in resetting your password. Some services may require added security, and in these cases, you may be asked to create an additional security key. Finally, a unique ID number will be assigned to your Midway Auto Supply credentials which will be used to identify your credentials and associated information. 

At some Midway Auto Supply sites, Midway Auto Supply collects personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. We may also collect demographic information, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites. Information collected on Midway Auto Supply may be combined with information obtained from other Midway Auto Supply services and other companies. 

We may collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the links you click and other actions taken in connection with Midway Auto Supply sites and services. We also collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring Web site addresses. 

Some Midway Auto Supply services may be co-branded and offered in conjunction with another company. If you register for or use such services, both Midway Auto Supply and the other company may receive information collected in conjunction with the co-branded services. 

Use of your Personal Information

Midway Auto Supply collects and uses your personal information to operate Midway Auto Supply and deliver the services you have requested. These services may include the display of customized content and advertising based upon the information we have collected. In order to provide services in conjunction with other Midway Auto Supply products or services, personal information collected on Midway Auto Supply may be accessed and used by other Midway Auto Supply services as necessary to provide such services. Any use of such information within Midway Auto Supply will remain subject to the limitations of this privacy statement. 

We also use your personal information to communicate with you. We may send certain mandatory service communications such as welcome letters, billing reminders, information on technical service issues, and security announcements. Some Midway Auto Supply services, including Midway Auto Supply Internet Access and Midway Auto Supply Hotmail, may send periodic member letters that are considered part of the service. We may also occasionally send you product surveys or promotional mailings to inform you of other products or services available from Midway Auto Supply and its affiliates. 

Midway Auto Supply does not sell, rent or lease its Midway Auto Supply customer lists to third parties. We may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your personal information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. We do not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent. 

We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose. 

Midway Auto Supply may access and/or disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Midway Auto Supply or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Midway Auto Supply, including its Midway Auto Supply family of Web sites; or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Midway Auto Supply services or members of the public. 

Personal information collected on this site may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Midway Auto Supply or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. Midway Auto Supply abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union. 

Control of your Personal Information

We offer you choices for the collection, use and sharing of your personal information. You may choose not to receive marketing material from Midway Auto Supply or on behalf of external third party business partners. You may also stop the delivery of future promotional e-mail from Midway Auto Supply by following the specific instructions in the e-mail you receive. 

You may subscribe and unsubscribe to Midway Auto Supply Newsletters.  In addition, each Midway Auto Supply newsletter you receive will have instructions on how to unsubscribe prominently mentioned in it. 

These communications choices do not apply to mandatory service communications that are considered part of certain Midway Auto Supply services, which you may receive periodically unless you cancel the service. 

You may have the ability to view or edit your personal information 

  * If you wish to update your Midway Auto Supply profile information, change your password, view the unique ID associated with your credentials, or close certain Midway Auto Supply accounts, please visit Midway Auto Supply Account Services. 
  * If you have a billing account you can add to or update the information through the Account Update. 
  * If you have created a public profile on Midway Auto Supply, you may also edit or delete information in your public profile.. 

Some services offered on Midway Auto Supply may collect personal information that is not accessible via the links above. However, in such cases, you may be able to access that information through alternative means of access described by the service. Or you can write us by using our Web form, and we will contact you within 30 days regarding your request. 

Security of your Personal Information

Midway Auto Supply is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access, which are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit card number or password) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. 

Use of Cookies

Midway Auto Supply uses "cookies" to enable you to sign in to Midway Auto Supply services and to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies contain information that can later be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.  

Midway Auto Supply uses cookies to store your preferences and other information on your computer in order to save you time by eliminating the need to repeatedly enter the same information and to display your personalized content and appropriate advertising on your later visits to Midway Auto Supply.  

When you sign in to a site using your Midway Auto Supply credentials, the Midway Auto Supply stores your unique ID number, and the time you signed in, in an encrypted cookie on your hard disk. This cookie allows you to move from page to page at the site without having to sign in again on each page. When you sign out, these cookies are deleted from your computer. The network also uses cookies to improve the sign in experience. For example, your e-mail address may be stored in a cookie that will remain on your computer after you sign out. This cookie allows your e-mail address to be pre-populated, so that you will only need to type your password the next time you sign in. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of Midway Auto Supply sites and services that depend on cookies. 

Use of Web Beacons

Midway Auto Supply Web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons - sometimes called single-pixel gifs - that allow Midway Auto Supply to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. Midway Auto Supply may include Web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or Midway Auto Supply Newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. 

Midway Auto Supply may also place Web beacons from third parties on our site in order to compile aggregated statistics and to help determine the effectiveness of our joint promotional or advertising campaigns. Midway Auto Supply prohibits Web beacons on our site from being used by third parties to access your personal information. 

Finally, Midway Auto Supply may work with other companies that advertise on Midway Auto Supply to place Web beacons on their sites in order to allow us to develop statistics on how often clicking on an advertisement on Midway Auto Supply results in a purchase or other action on the advertiser’s site. 

Use of Third Party Ad Networks

The majority of the online banner advertisements you see on Midway Auto Supply Web pages are displayed by Midway Auto Supply. However, Midway Auto Supply allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to display advertisements on Midway Auto Supply Web pages. Some of these ad networks may place a persistent cookie on your computer in order to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad networks may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. Midway Auto Supply does not have access to the cookies that may be placed by the third-party ad servers or ad networks. 

Controlling “Spam” or Unsolicited E-mail

Midway Auto Supply is concerned about controlling unsolicited commercial e-mail, or "spam." Midway Auto Supply has a strict policy prohibiting the use of Midway Auto Supply e-mail account to send spam. To read more about this policy. Midway Auto Supply will not sell, lease or rent its e-mail subscriber lists to third parties. While Midway Auto Supply continues to actively review and implement new technology, such as expanded filtering features, there is no currently available technology that will totally prevent the sending and receiving of unsolicited e-mail. 

Enforcement of this Privacy Statement

If you have questions regarding this statement, you should first contact Midway Auto Supply. 

Changes to this Statement

We will occasionally update this Privacy Statement to reflect changes in our services and customer feedback. When we posts changes to this Statement, you will see the word "updated" next to the Midway Auto Supply Privacy Statement link on the front page of Midway Auto Supply. If there are material changes to this Statement or in how Midway Auto Supply will use your personal information, we will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. We encourage you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Midway Auto Supply is protecting your information. 

Contact Information

Midway Auto Supply welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Statement. If you have questions about this Statement or believe that we have not adhered to it, please contact Midway Auto Supply Privacy by using our Web form. 

Midway Auto Supply Privacy  
P.O. Box 4415  
Dallas, TX 75208  
1-866-MIDWAY-1  

Critical Performance Errors  
You may occasionally see a message informing you of a critical performance error in Midway Auto Supply.
